{"test_questions": [[{"question": "This type of solid is egg-shaped and can be created by revolving an ellipse around one of its axes:", "opta": "Ellipsoid", "optb": "Torus", "optc": "Cone", "optd": "Cylinder", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Some of the common terms used to describe technical drawing include:", "opta": "Drafting", "optb": "Engineering Graphics", "optc": "Engineering Drawing", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An architect often relies on a ________ to complete the set of technical drawings used in the design of an office building.", "opta": "technical illustrator", "optb": "artist", "optc": "drafter", "optd": "construction superintendent", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In oblique sketches, the most commonly used angles for receding lines are:", "opta": "15 or 30 degrees", "optb": "25 or 30 degrees", "optc": "30 or 45 degrees", "optd": "45 or 60 degrees", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A drafter who develops technical drawings of a highway overpass would most likely be a ________ drafter.", "opta": "architectural", "optb": "civil", "optc": "mechanical", "optd": "process piping", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "These types of projectors converge at a vanishing point:", "opta": "Perspective", "optb": "Parallel", "optc": "Orthographic", "optd": "Oblique", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A ________ is the person responsible for verifying that the drawings in a project set are free of mistakes.", "opta": "client", "optb": "CAD trainee", "optc": "receptionist", "optd": "checker", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This type of solid has two bases that are parallel equal polygons:", "opta": "Pyramid", "optb": "Prism", "optc": "Cone", "optd": "Torus", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An oil refinery relies on which type of drafter to maintain and update the technical piping drawings used for the construction and maintenance of the facility.", "opta": "architectural", "optb": "civil", "optc": "process piping", "optd": "electrical", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When designing a home for a client, one of the most important pre-design considerations that an architect needs to address is ________.", "opta": "how much money the client is willing to spend.", "optb": "the site on which the house is to sit", "optc": "the nearest grocery store", "optd": "whether or not there is a curb and gutter system", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is formed where three or more surfaces intersect:", "opta": "Oblique", "optb": "Line", "optc": "Edge", "optd": "Vertex", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Department of Labor's Bureau of Labor Statistics predicts that some of the best opportunities for employment in our near future will be for students who ________.", "opta": "drop out of high school", "optb": "graduate from high school and go right into the workforce", "optc": "obtain a two year technical degree from a community or junior college", "optd": "earn a B.S. degree in psychology", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Three dimensional models are often used in the design process to ________.", "opta": "help the client understand the overall design concept", "optb": "help the client select a color for their carpet", "optc": "provide the client with a model which they can use to impress their friends", "optd": "determine the quantity of brick needed to build the house", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Students can complete an associate's degree in drafting which normally takes about ________ years to complete.", "opta": "one", "optb": "two", "optc": "three", "optd": "four", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This is used in drawings to represent the edge of a solid object:", "opta": "Angle", "optb": "Vertex", "optc": "Surface", "optd": "Line", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The daily workload of a ________ drafter would generally include technical drawings of machine parts.", "opta": "architectural", "optb": "civil", "optc": "electrical", "optd": "mechanical", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This type of solid has a polygon for a base and triangular lateral faces that intersect at a vertex:", "opta": "Pyramid", "optb": "Prism", "optc": "Cone", "optd": "Torus", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}